YYeTs-人人影视
中英 双语 字幕
■
翻译：青椒  木恺  持久君  CQQ  gracyyyyyy
翻译：考拉是S妹  静妹粒  拉面配卤蛋
■
时间轴：阿丹  凌晨相见
校对：阿飘
■
后期：灰灰是菇凉    总监：钛合金狗牙飘
天堂执法者
第四季 第九集
感恩节
开球  开球
Hut, hut!
来追我啊
Try and catch me!
厉害
Come on!
集合  集合  集合
Huddle, huddle, huddle!
快跑  快跑
Let's go! Let's go!
防守  防守
Hut, hut!
给我这么厉害的一双手点赞
I just want to thank my hands for being so awesome.
-抓得好  队长  -多谢夸奖
- Nice catch, Captain. - Thank you.
他来这里干什么
Why is he here?
他的家人不是都在芝加哥嘛
I mean, uh, his family's all in Chicago.
他没地方去
He had no place to go.
所以你就邀请他来参加家庭橄榄球赛吗
So you invited him to a family football game?
对啊
Yeah.
我明白你们共度了难关  增进了感情
Oh. Look, I understand you guys had a bonding moment,
但是你别忘了  这个男人
but you're aware that that's the guy
向州长打了你的小报告
that ratted you out to the governor?
友情提醒一下
I'm just reminding you.
今天可是感恩节
I mean, it's Thanksgiving, okay?
就当我心胸宽广吧
I mean, call me the bigger man.
-他们在等你呢  -快来  集合了
- They're waiting for you. - Come on, let's huddle!
来吧  兄弟  集合了
Come on, guys. Let's bring it in. Huddle, huddle!
42比35  我们领先
42-35, our favor.
只要保持住  我们就赢定了
Listen, we hold 'em here, the game's ours. All right?
行  压制住他们  比赛就是我们的
All right, now we got 'em. This is the play.
丹尼  你在我右边待命  随时准备
Danny, I want you to line up on my right, run a post,
你们两个在我左右  到时候从两边...
you two line up on either side of me. I want you to cross...
把球给我就行  我来负责得分
Just-Just give me the ball. I'll get it into the end zone.
你菊花里要是自带喷气机
The only way you're getting the ball
我们才考虑把球传给你
is if you got a jet pack up your culo, okay?
数三声一起说守住  一二三
On three-- defense! One, two, three.
-守住  -好嘞  -出发
- Defense! - All right! - Let's go!
来吧  秒杀他们
Here we go, take it down.
来吧  弱鸡六人组
Let's go. Come on. Easy six!
放心吧
Man, I got you.
开始吧  准备好了吗
Here we go. Here we go. Ready?
传球给我
Give me the ball.
-准备  开球  -游戏开始
- Set... hut! - Here we go!
不  别是威廉姆斯  不...
No! Not Williams. No...
听我说  我们要团结起来
All-State QB. We're all tied up.
再触地得分一次就赢了
Next touchdown wins.
等一下  等等
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
提醒
上午9:45  放火鸡进烤箱
-不行  我得走了  -去哪里
- That's it I gotta go. - Whoa, whoa, go where?
去哪里  你在说什么
Go where? What are you talking about?
我得去  去把火鸡放进烤箱里
I gotta, I gotta put the turkey in the oven.
我天  你要干什么  干什么啊你
Oh-oh! What are you doing? What are you doing?
你今天还想不想吃了
You want to eat today or what?
让玛丽把那玩意放进那东西里就行
Oh! Have Mary put the thing in the thing.
-还用你亲自去啊  -玛丽是打下手的
- What are you doing? - Mary's the prep cook.
你们都盯着我干什么
What are you all looking at me for?
打下手的厨师不能负责填充火鸡  明白吗
The prep cook doesn't get to stuff the turkey, okay?
-这是我的任务  -你来真的啊
- This is my operation. - Oh, come on, are you serious?
难以置信  我们还在打比赛呢
This is unbelievable. We got a game here.
我十分钟后就回来
I'll be back in ten minutes!
麦格瑞特家
怎么回事
What the hell?
还没解冻
It didn't thaw.
什么
What?!
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
-你昨晚从冰箱里拿出来了吗  -拿了
- Did you take it out of the freezer last night? - Yeah.
然后放进冷水里了吗
And you put it in cold water?
当然啦
Yeah. For sure.
你放进冷水里没有
Did you put it in cold water?
没有
No.
我忘记了
No, I-I completely forgot.
别生我气  别生气
Please don't be mad. Please.
你知道吗  我让你来打下手
You know what? I knew something like this
就知道一定会出这种状况
would happen if I made you my prep cook.
你要是早就知道
Well, then why'd you make me your prep cook
为什么还要让我帮忙
if you knew this was gonna happen?
你逼我的啊
You forced me to make you my prep cook.
你说自己光负责搞定土豆泥不过瘾
You told me that mashing potatoes wasn't enough responsibility.
想多干点事
You wanted more responsibility.
所以我就让你打下手了
And I made you my prep cook.
你说得对
You're right.
好吧  我很抱歉
Okay, but listen. I'm sorry.
琼昨晚太能闹腾了
Joan was so fussy last night.
一直都不肯睡觉
I couldn't-I couldn't get her down.
我向你道歉
And I apologize.
马上就来
Yes, I'm coming!
帮我个忙
Okay, uh, do me a favor.
打开烤箱  先预热
Put the oven on, get the sides started.
我再想办法吧
And I'll-I'll figure something out.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving!
黛比姑妈
Aunt Deb?
快来抱一抱
Come here and give me a hug.
你怎么会来这里
What are you doing here?
都这么多年没见你了
Well, it's been years since I've seen you,
所以我就想来看看你
and I figured it's high time i paid you a visit.
你真漂亮
You look fantastic.
你也是啊  快让我看看
Well, look at you. Let me see...
怎么
What?
你看到什么了
What do you got?
-我看到这里有白发了哦  -是啊
- I see a little little gray fleck right there. - Oh, yeah,
-是有些  喜欢吗  -还不赖
- a little bit. You like that? - Yeah, yeah, I like it.
让你看起来非常成熟卓越
I think it makes you look very distinguished.
-谢谢  -没什么
- Thank you very much. - Yeah.
不过文身就不怎么样了
The tattoos not so much.
黛比姑妈
Aunt Deb?
是玛丽和她的小宝宝
Oh! It's Mary and her little lamb.
亲爱的
Oh, honey! Oh!
没想到你会来
I didn't know you were coming.
你知道她会来吗
Did you know she was coming?
完全不知道
No, I had no idea.
见到你们真开心
Oh, it's so great to see you guys.
坐下好好聊聊吧
Well, come on. Let's sit down.
黛比姑妈  我们也很想坐下
Aunt Deb, we'd love to, but we're in
不过我们面临着厨房危机
the middle of a culinary crisis right now.
我们把火鸡搞砸了
We, um, screwed up the turkey.
还冻着呢
It's still frozen.
"我们"
"We."
看来我来得正是时候
Well, then I got here just in time.
我是麦格瑞特  好  马上来
McGarrett. Yeah, okay, I'm on the way.
我得走了
I gotta go.
什么  你这就要走了
What, you're leaving already?
有工作  我得走了
It's work. I gotta go.
拜托你们搞定那只火鸡  好吗
Listen, can you handle the bird, please?
搞笑呢  交给我们妥妥的  快去吧
Are you kidding? We got it covered. Go. Go.
记得要及时跟我汇报进度
I want constant updates, though.
-好吗  -好的  快走吧
- All right? - All right, okay, go, go.
我今天能吃到火鸡的概率是多少
So, what are the odds of me actually eating turkey today?
十分之一还是五分之一
What do I got, a 10% chance? 20%?
放松点好吗  我姑妈黛比在那里呢
Will you relax, okay? My Aunt Deb is there.
她会搞定一切的
She's gonna figure everything out.
姑妈黛比  你爸爸的妹妹
Oh, your Aunt Deb. Your father's sister.
你妈妈假死之后照顾玛丽的那位吗
The one who took care of Mary after your mother faked her death?
-你有个很大的问题  -我吗
- There's something seriously wrong with you, you know that? - Me?
你很喜欢提醒我那件事
You like reminding me of that?
为什么你那么喜欢提
Why would you like reminding me of that?
法医
-那是事实啊  -是  那是事实
- It's the truth. - Yes, it's the truth.
事实的确如此
Yes, it's the truth.
黛比姑妈独自把玛丽拉扯大
Aunt Deb who raised Mary all by herself.
她肯定很不容易
That must have been trying.
你根本无法想象
You don't know the half of it.
为了玛丽这个孩子
She walked away from a record deal
她拒绝了一份唱片合约
when that kid got thrown in her lap, you know that?
-她还唱过歌  -你不知道吗
- She was a singer? - You didn't know that?
我不知道啊
I did not.
那时她已经当了二十年伴唱歌手了
Yeah, she struggled as a backup singer for 20 years,
终于要苦尽甘来有所改变
and she finally got a big break,
但因为玛丽的出现
but she walked away from it
她毅然决然地放弃了
as soon as Mary came into the picture.
-就那样  -就那样  兄弟
- Just like that, huh? Just like that, man.
她知道要是她一年中有半年在演出
She knew she couldn't raise a kid
她就不可能好好养育这个孩子
if she was gonna be on the road half the year,
所以她放弃了
so she quit.
然后成为了一名歌唱教练
She became a singing coach instead.
-凯瑟琳  -来了
- Oh, ah, Catherine. - Yeah?
什么状况
What's up?
说说我们的发现
All right, here's what we know:
四名渔夫出海拖捕箭鱼
so, a four-man crew was out trolling for some skipjack
结果拖上来了这玩意
when they hooked this.
170升的油桶  不像是平常的渔获
Huh. 45-gallon barrel. That's not your usual bycatch.
让我猜猜  里面有具尸体
Let me guess. There's a-a body in here.
打开看看不就知道了
Just take a look.
好吧
All right.
不是吧
Oh, no.
他的其他残肢呢
Where's the rest of him?
想买什么  女士们
Help you ladies?
我们想买只火鸡
Yeah, we need a turkey.
你们知道今天是感恩节吧
You know it's Thanksgiving, right?
头罩男  我们不需要嘲讽
Yeah. Look, hairnet, we don't need sarcasm,
只要火鸡  好吗
all we need is a turkey, okay?
求你了  我们真的很急
Please? We're desperate.
我找找看
Let me check.
来  亲爱的  来抱抱  不哭啊
Here, honey, come here. No-no-no-no-no-no.
来  来抱抱  抱抱啊
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
-你确定  -当然了  来
- Are you sure? - Oh, yeah. Come on.
小宝贝
My baby.
你真会带孩子
You're like a baby whisperer.
我还是有几招的嘛
I got my moves.
-是吗  能教教我吗  -怎么了
- Oh, yeah? Can I have some? - What is it?
我不知道  我觉得有些应付不过来
I don't know. I just, I really feel like I'm in over my head.
你照顾我时也会有这种感觉吗
Did you ever feel like that with me?
-一直都有  -真的吗
- Always. - Really?
看来我折腾得你很惨啊
So I'm guessing I didn't make life very easy for you.
这么说吧
Well, let me put it this way.
小孩子都是这样的
You had your moments.
你是怎么撑过来的  黛比
How'd you do it, Deb?
我根本不知道自己在做什么
I mean, I feel like i have no clue what I'm doing.
你以为我当时就知道吗
You think I did?
亲爱的  我一直是即兴发挥的
Oh, honey, I-I was winging it the whole time.
现在还心有余悸
And it-it was scary.
当妈是世界上最难的工作
Being a mom is the hardest job in whole wide world.
但我觉得没有人
But, you know, I can't think of anybody
能比你更胜任这份工作
who's better suited for it than you.
你心很宽
You got a big heart.
又很聪明
You're smart.
你要做的就是全心全意地爱她
All you have to do is love her with everything you got
一切就会好起来了
and you're gonna be fine.
小甜心
Hey, sweetie.
好了  给你
Okay, here we are.
开玩笑吧
Oh, you're kidding.
这就是最好的了吗  垃圾堆里捡来的吧
That's the best you got? The runt of the litter?
下次早点来买
Hey, next time plan ahead.
谢谢你的好提议
Thank you for that sage advice.
日本  东京
你说什么  表哥
What are you saying, cuz?
我说结束了
I'm saying it's over.
我们从东京回来之后
After we got back from Tokyo,
就抓住了迈克・西村的同伙余党
we took down the rest of Michael Noshimuri's allies.
那个帮派已经消失了  科诺
That faction's gone, Kono.
他们已经玩完了
They're finished.
亚当那有消息吗
Any closer to finding Adam?
就我目前掌握的线索来看
Um, from what I've been able to piece together,
我觉得他在西雅图
I think he may be in Seattle.
所以我今天就飞去那里
So I'm flying there today.
好的  你现在不用再警惕四周
Okay. It's gonna be easier for you to move around
四处走动也比之前容易一些
now that you don't have to look over your shoulder.
所以就是说
So I guess that means
你会在三万尺的高空过感恩节[9150米]
you'll be spending Thanksgiving at 30,000 feet.
餐桌上没有你感觉空荡荡的
Table's gonna feel empty without you.
明年我会在的
I'll be there next year.
我保证
I promise.
我要走了
Hey, look, I should get going.
我可不想误机
I don't want to miss my flight.
祝你好运
Good luck.
谢谢  表哥  谢谢你为我做的一切
Mahalo, cuz... for everything.
我刚刚和科诺打过电话
I just got off the phone with Kono.
她准备去西雅图
She's heading to Seattle.
有新线索吗
New lead?
拭目以待吧
We'll see.
有什么新发现
So where are we at?
据方所说
Okay, according to Fong,
装死者的桶里放满了碱液
the barrel our vic was found in was filled with lye.
惊奇吧  具有强腐蚀性
Surprise, it's highly corrosive.
便宜又好买
It's also cheap and easy to get.
-麦克斯尸检完了吗  -是的
- Max finish the autopsy? - He did.
看他在受害者脖子上找到了什么
And look what he found around the vic's neck.
这是什么  医用身份识别带
What is that, a medical alert ID?
名叫凯尔・鲁索  生于1978年5月9日
Says the name is Kyle Russo, D.O.B.: 5-9-78.
美国特勤处
凯尔・鲁索
受害者是特勤处的
Our vic was Secret Service.
特勤处驻扎点
大威基基希尔顿度假酒店
打扰了  戴文・坎贝尔
Excuse me, Devon Campbell.
我是史蒂夫・麦格瑞特
Steve McGarrett.
她是凯瑟琳・罗林斯  我们是五零特遣队的
Catherine Rollins. Five-O.
办事处说了你们要过来  抱歉稍等一下
Field office said you guys were coming. Hang on a sec. Sorry.
-忙碌的一天  -看得出来  怎么了吗
- Busy day. - Yeah, we can see that. What's going on?
总统正在来这的路上
The president's on his way to the Island.
他今天晚些时候会到
He'll be here later today.
他通常都在特区过感恩节
He usually does Thanksgiving in DC,
但是两天前他决定要来这儿
but two nights ago he decided he wanted to come here.
没给我们多少时间  但是我们会准备好的
Doesn't leave us much prep time, but... we'll be ready.
有什么能帮你的吗
What can I do for you?
我们得谈谈你的一个探员  凯尔・鲁索
We need to talk to you about one of your agents, Kyle Russo.
他怎么了
Yeah, what about him?
他昨天被谋杀了
He was murdered yesterday.
什么
What?
今早在海边
We found his remains in a barrel
我们在一个汽油桶里找到了他的部分遗体
just offshore this morning.
-有嫌疑人吗  -没有
- You got any suspects? - No, sir, we don't.
但作案手法看起来很专业
But everything is pointing to a professional hit.
你最后一次跟鲁索探员联系是什么时候
When was the last time you spoke with Agent Russo?
我昨晚收到他的简讯
I got a text from him last night.
说他今早要去北岸
He said he was headed up to the North Shore this morning
检查总统会前往的一家书店
to check on a bookstore POTUS might want to visit.
他什么时候给你发的信息
What time did he send that text?
九点后不久  怎么了
A little after 9:00. Why?
法医推测的死亡时间
Because our M.E. puts time of death someplace
大概在五点到七点之间
5:00 and 7:00.
也就是说杀害鲁索探员的凶手
That means Agent Russo's killer
拿走了他的手机  给你发了信息
took his phone, sent you that text so you wouldn't
这样你就不会因为他今早没出现
be suspicious when he didn't show up
-而心生怀疑  -没错
- for work this morning. - Right.
天呐
My God.
坎贝尔探员  怎么了
Agent Campbell. What?
我们所有探员的手机里
All our agents have intel on POTUS's trip
都有总统此次行程的情报
stored on their phone.
精确到半分钟的行程表
Itinerary down to the half-minute,
车队的行驶路线
path of the motorcade,
以及应急方案
emergency protocols.
要是那些情报落入坏人之手
If that intel has fallen into the wrong hands,
总统的安全就会受到威胁了
then we have a threat to the president.
空军一号
距到达还有六小时
作为预防措施  我们正在变更车队路线
As a precaution, we're changing the path of the motorcade
以及紧急撤退路线
ascape routes.
火奴鲁鲁警局正帮我们封锁全境
HPD's helping us lock everything down
特警队将作为特勤局的后援
and SWAT's gonna back up our Counter Assault Team.
感谢你能过来  队长
Thank you for coming, Captain.
没事  我们已经全员出动了
No problem. I got everybody on this.
总统套房
希尔顿夏威夷度假村
好吧
All right.
-需要我们干些什么  -开门见山
- What do you want from my team? - Plain and simple.
抓住那个杀了凯尔・鲁索的混蛋
I need you to find the son of a bitch that killed Kyle Russo.
在这儿  我没有资源  没法调查
Now, I don't have assets in place to run an investigation.
现在我唯一关心的
Right now, my only concern has to be
只有总统的安保
the president's safety and security.
没有比这更重要的
I have no other priorities.
好吧  我需要重走一遍鲁索的行程
All right, I need to, uh, retrace Russo's steps.
能告诉我他昨天一天的行程吗
What can you tell me about his activities yesterday?
他昨天大部分时间都在凯卢阿
He was in Kailua for most of it.
总统到达以后
POTUS stays at
会下榻在那儿的一处私人住宅
a private home out there when he's in town.
鲁索当时正在检查当地居民
Russo was looking into some of the residents
-看有没有威胁存在  -他跟你报告了吗
- to see if any of 'em posed a threat. - He check in with you?
当时有个人
He said there was one guy
他说想做些背景调查
he wanted to run some background on,
也许...要再交谈一次
maybe... maybe talk to again.
他给你那人的名字了吗
He give you a name?
凯斯・诺兰  他就说了名字
Keith Nolan. That's all he gave me.
显然  这家伙在那儿租了间房
Apparently, this guy's renting a house out there
距离总统要下榻的地方不足四百米
less than a quarter of a mile from the one pOTUS is staying in.
鲁索说也许没什么
Russo said it was probably nothing.
我昨晚收到信息的时候
When I got that text last night,
我以为那家伙已经排除威胁了
I just assumed the guy checked out.
也许的确如此
Yeah, maybe he did.
但是如果鲁索把他当作潜在威胁
But if Russo considered him a potential threat,
我们就得跟他谈谈
he's somebody we want to talk to.
好的
All right.
凯卢阿  凯斯・诺兰租住处
诺兰先生
Mr. Nolan?
我是五零特遣队的史蒂夫・麦格瑞特
Steve McGarrett, Five-O.
能跟你谈谈吗
Can we talk to you?
炉子上还烧着开水
Boiling water on the stove.
那家伙走得还挺急
The guy, uh, took off in a hurry.
那可是颗大子弹
That is a big bullet.
这是北约制式步枪弹
This is a NATO 7.62 sniper round.
精确射程一千米
It's accurate up to 1,000 meters.
也许鲁索真有所图
So maybe Russo was onto something.
五零特遣队
Hey! Five-O!
把手放到我能看见的地方  你是谁
Let me see your hands, right now. Who are you?
我叫希拉・希克斯
I'm Sheila Hicks.
我就住这条街上
I live up the street.
我替房主看着这房子
I look after the house for the owner.
我能把手放下了吗  拜托了
Can I put my hands down now, please?
当然可以  很抱歉
Of course you can. I'm sorry.
你...
Uh... you, uh,
你有没有看到过
you happen to get a look at the guy
最近住这儿的那个人
that's been staying here?
诺兰先生吗
Mr. Nolan?
看到了  他昨天早上住进来的
Yeah, he got in yesterday morning.
他是从毛伊岛来的
He's from Maui.
可友好了
He's a very friendly guy.
只不过是我女儿
Oh, it's just my daughter!
过来  小甜心
Come here, sweetie.
妈妈  怎么了
Mom, what's going on?
没事
It's okay.
他们是五零特遣队的
These men are Five-O.
我们只是想问几个
We just have some questions
关于租这房子的那位先生的问题
about the man who's renting this house.
能告诉我们他长什么样吗
Can you tell us what he looked like?
当然  他大概四十多岁
Sure. He's 40s.
一米八三
Six feet.
黑发  对了  你知道么
Black hair. Oh, and you know what?
他脖子后面有个纹身
And he had a tattoo on the back of his neck.
那这个人呢
How 'bout this guy?
-你  你见过他吗  -见过
- You, uh... you seen him? - Yes.
我看到他昨天和诺兰先生在外面谈话
I saw him and Mr.Nolan talking outside yesterday.
那是什么时候
What time was that?
刚过四点吧
Little after 4:00?
他并没待很久
You know, he didn't stay very long.
大概就三四分钟
Maybe three, four minutes.
他就走了
And then he left,
之后诺兰先生也走了
and Mr. Nolan took off right after that.
不过  我从那之后就再也没见过他们俩了
But I-I haven't seen either of them since.
好吧  那你呢
Okay, how 'bout you?
你看到什么了吗
You see anything?
我才到这一小时
I just got in an hour ago.
她是为了过节才回来的
She flew in for the holiday.
我的安德莉娅宝贝前几个月一直在旅行
My Andrea's been traveling for the last few months
但是她想回来和妈妈一起过感恩节
but she wanted to spend Thanksgiving with her mom.
真贴心
Oh, that's nice.
真贴心  钥匙给你
That's nice. Uh... here's your keys.
-谢谢  -抱歉刚刚吓着你了
- Thank you. - Sorry about the scare,
谢谢你的帮助
and thanks for your help.
如果你们还需要帮助的话  到隔壁找我
You need anything, I'm right next door.
-多事的邻居是警察之友  -对
- Nosy neighbor is a cop's best friend, right? - Right.
好的  谢了
All right, thank you.
好吧  毛伊岛警局的记录里
All right, so Maui PD has no record
没有任何一个凯斯・诺兰
of anyone named Keith Nolan
符合我们的描述
that matches our description.
根据运输安全局的记录
And according to TSA,
昨天抵达这儿的人里也没有这么个名字
nobody flew in yesterday under that name.
所以让我来乱猜一下
So I am taking a wild guess,
"凯斯・诺兰"只是个化名
"Keith Nolan" is an alias.
好吧  那鲁索...
All right, so Russo...
他到这里来巡查
he's out here clearing houses,
遇见了一个自称为"凯斯・诺兰"的家伙
he meets a guy who calls himself "Keith Nolan",
他发现了什么
he gets a vibe.
好吧  我觉得
All right, I'm thinking maybe
也许诺兰察觉到鲁索盯上他了
Nolan could sense that Russo was onto him.
于是他跟踪鲁索  然后杀了他
He follows him and he kills him.
这是个不错的理论
It's a good theory.
如果我们是对的  我就只有一个疑问
If we're right, I only have one question:
这个家伙在特勤局公开之前
this guy had to have known the president was coming
就得知道总统要来
before the Secret Service went public with it.
而这是个机密的消息
That's closely-guarded info.
他怎么知道的
How did he get it?
先遣队已经着陆了36个小时了
Advance team's been on the ground for 36 hours.
也许他是推测出来的
Maybe he figured it out.
我是麦格瑞特
Yeah, McGarrett.
等一下  你说什么
Wait a minute, what?
什么意思  她被...
What do you mean, she was...
她什么时候被抓的
When was she arrested?
玛丽被抓了
Oh, Mary got arrested.
-不  是我姑妈  -你姑妈被抓了
- No, my aunt. - Your aunt got arrested?
这我倒是没料到
I didn't see that coming.
火奴鲁鲁警局
你好
Hi.
谢谢
Thanks.
给我点时间
A second.
你还好吗
You okay?
还不错
I'm fine.
很好
Good.
想告诉我发生了什么吗
Do you want to tell me what happened?
好吧  我...
Well, I...
我想买些大麻  然后...
I needed some grass, and, uh...
我怎么知道那家伙是个缉毒的
how was I supposed to know the guy was a narc?
-什么  -如果不是药房的那群法西斯
- What? - I wouldn't even be here
我才不会沦落至此呢
if it weren't for those fascists at the dispensary.
他们也不会拿走我的卡
They wouldn't take my card.
药房
The dispensary?
-你...-柜台后面那家伙告诉我
- What... - Yeah, and the guy behind the counter
找谁可以买到大麻
told me where I could find some,
然后我就碰上缉毒刑警了...
and then I run into this narc...
暂停一下  等一下
Okay, stop, please. For a minute.
怎么了
What?
-我们倒回去一下  -好
- Can we go back? - Yeah.
你为什么会有张医用大麻的卡
Why do you have a medical marijuana card?
我有白内障
I have cataracts.
你有白内障吗
You have cataracts?
对啊
Yes.
白内障  人老了就会有的
Cataracts, that's what happens when you get old.
你和我说的是实话吗
Are you telling me the truth?
一半的人在我这个年龄都会得白内障
Look... half the people my age get them.
黛比
Deborah.
-史蒂芬...-我是个警察
- Steven... - I'm a cop.
我的工作就是读出别人的想法
I read people for a living.
你对我没有实话实说
You're not telling me everything.
我本不想这么做的
This isn't how I wanted to do this.
做什么
Do what?
好吧...
Okay, um...
几个月前  我觉得不太舒服
A couple of months ago, I wasn't feeling so good,
而且  我一直很累
and, um... I was tired all the time,
恶心  头疼
nauseous, headaches...
所以我去看了医生
So I went to the doctor
他们给我做了一大堆检查  然后...
and they ran a whole bunch of tests, and, um...
结果是...
Turns out...
我的脑袋里有个肿瘤
I have a tumor in my brain.
你得了癌症
You have cancer?
是的
Yeah.
情况有多糟
How bad is it?
不太好
It's bad.
好吧
Okay, all right.
你有什么打算
What's the plan?
想怎么治疗
What's the course of treatment?
没有治疗
Well... there is none.
什么都没有...
There is none, it's... it's...
那太遥远了
it's too far along.
不  但是  你知道的
No, but... you know,
化疗  放疗
chemo, radiation...
不  我们讨论过那个
No, we talked about that,
但是我...我决定不做治疗
but I... I decided against it.
为什么
Why?
因为他们说这不管用...
Because they said it wouldn't work...
所以我...
so I...
所以你就  你就直接放弃了吗
All right, so you just... that's it? You just give up?
-你就打算这么做了吗  -不  等等
- Is that what you're gonna do? - No, no, no, no, wait.
你不能放弃  你不能
Cause you can't do that. No, you can't,
你得...你得积极治疗
because that's what... You gotta fight this.
听我说
Listen to me.
我不希望把我所剩下的时间
I don't want to spend whatever time I have left
浪费在医院里
in some hospital,
大把大把地吃那些有毒的药
getting pumped full of poison
让自己这么难受  好吗
and feeling crappy all the time, okay?
我不想那样
That's not how I want to do this.
这是我的决定
This is what I've decided.
我懂的...
I know...
好吧
Okay.
所以你才来这里的  对吗
That's why you're here, isn't it?
你想跟我们道别
You wanted to come say good-bye to us.
听着  你不能告诉你妹妹
Listen, uh... you can't say anything to your sister.
什么  等等
Wait, what?
你不能这样  黛比  这不公平
You can't do that, Deb. That's not fair.
你不能不告诉她
You can't keep this from her.
不  我会告诉她的
No, I-I'm gonna tell her,
-我只是在等合适的时机  好吗  -好吧
- I'm just waiting for the right moment, okay? - Okay.
你还是赶紧回去工作吧
Look... you better get back to work.
我还得去作笔录呢
I've still gotta get booked.
你不用去
You're not getting booked.
我要去
I am getting booked.
我不要任何特殊待遇  好吗
I don't want any special treatment, okay?
我是认真的
I'm serious.
好吧  好吧
Fine. Fine.
那你就去作笔录吧
You're getting booked.
很好
Good.
等你处理完了我会找人来接你的
I'll send someone to pick you up when you're through.
给我找个帅小哥来  行吗
Make sure he's good-looking, okay?
-孩子  我爱你  -我也爱你
- Kid, I love you. - I love you, too.
会好起来的
It's gonna be all right.
五零特遣队总部
我看了火奴鲁鲁警局调出来的监控录像
So I'm running through some footage that HPD pulled.
总算在杜克市场吃东西的小摊那里
I was able to track kyle Russo's movements
找到了凯尔・鲁索的踪迹
from a food truck he ate at
你们的想法是正确的
through Duke's Marketplace, and you guys were right.
他被人跟踪了  戴棒球帽那个
He was followed. Guy in the baseball cap.
一米八三
All right, about six feet tall,
黑发  脖子后面有纹身
uh, black hair, tattoo on his neck.
与我们知道的描述相符
Matches our description.
继续放下去
All right, keep going.
停车车库
阿成  往回放一点
All right, Chin, roll it back
试试看能不能截取到
Let's see if you could snap in,
他脸部的清晰图像
get a clean frame of his face.
杀手名字是但丁・巴克福
Killer's name is Dante Barkov.
但丁・巴克福
他是个雇佣杀手
He's an assassin-for-hire.
不效忠于任何人
He has no allegiance to anybody.
你们打算怎么找他
What are you doing to find him?
我们已经发布了通缉令
Well, we have an alert out.
我们还在寻找岛上
We're also looking into any known associates
任何可能跟他有关联的人
he may have on the Island.
但目前为止对他的确切位置
But right now, we don't have any leads
还没有任何线索
on his exact whereabouts.
鉴于这种情况
Given the circumstances,
你的老板应该取消行程
your boss needs to cancel his trip.
不可能
That's not gonna happen.
无意冒犯  先生  我们的对手
All due respect, sir, we're not talking about
可不是一个拿着左轮手枪的枪手
a whack job with a six-shooter, here, okay?
这个人对总统来说是极大的威胁
This man represents a serious threat to the president.
先生们...
Gentlemen...
总统不会取消行程的
the president won't cancel.
想想这种行为的潜台词
I mean, think of the message it'd send.
潜台词
The message?
你觉不觉得这位先生没在跟我们说实话
You get the feeling this gentleman isn't telling us the truth?
你也觉得呀
Oh, do you get that feeling, too?
这次行程与感恩节无关  对吗
This trip is not about Thanksgiving, is it?
如果是的话
If it was, the president
因为这个人的存在
would turn his plane around and go home
总统肯定会让飞机调头回家的
because of a man like this.
你为什么不跟我们说实话
So why don't you level with us,
告诉我们这烟雾弹是为了什么
and tell us what this smoke screen is all about?
总统是来这里
The president is coming for a secret meeting
跟几个朝鲜人开秘密会议的
with a small group from North Korea.
这次是一对一的面谈
These are one-on-one talks
可能会导致裁军
which could lead to disarmament,
甚至是政权更迭
maybe even regime change.
代价太大了
The stakes are huge.
他不会取消行程的
He won't cancel.
先生们  不管我们怎么想
Gentlemen, whether we like it or not,
空军一号今晚六点就会降落
Air Force One is wheels down at 6:00 P.M.
如果你是对的
If you're right,
那么巴克福就仍然在谋划刺杀总统
Barkov is still planning to assassinate the president.
我们还有两个小时来把他找出来
We have two hours to find him.
空军一号
离着陆还有两小时
我刚跟方打完电话
I just got off the phone with Fong,
他觉得巴克福在处理凯尔・鲁索的尸体时
who thinks Barkov might have had some help
肯定找了人帮忙
in disposing of Kyle Russo's body.
作案手法看起来非常专业
It turns out that the M.O. is pretty specific.
首先
For starters,
凶手用的碱是钾碱
the lye that was used was actually potassium lye.
比一般使用的品种要少见
It's a lot less common than the regular kind.
而且加了水进行混合  加速了反应
Also, it was mixed with water, which speeds up the reaction.
我把这种作案手法跟旧案作了交叉比对
I cross-referenced this particular M.O.
找到了几个相似的犯案人员
with some old cases and got a few hits.
有没有跟巴克福有关联的
Anyone with a connection to Barkov?
只有一个
Just one.
拉斐尔・莫雷诺
Rafael Moreno.
他是阿尔巴尼亚罪案团伙的善后人员
He's a cleaner for an Albanian crime syndicate.
据说巴克福被他雇佣犯过几次案
Barkov allegedly did some jobs for him.
根据国际刑警的消息
Now, according to Interpol,
莫雷诺至少处理过十几具尸体
Moreno has disappeared at least a dozen bodies
在过去的18个月里
in the last 18 months.
国际刑警  拉斐尔・莫雷诺
所以  鲁索开始调查巴克福后
Okay, so Barkov kills Russo
就被他所杀
once Russo gets onto him,
但处理尸体这事巴克福不在行
but, uh, body disposal isn't exactly in his wheelhouse.
所以他打电话给这个叫拉斐尔的男人
So he calls his boy, Rafael,
让他启程飞往瓦胡岛去帮他
who hops a flight to Oahu to help out.
但事实是没有任何拉斐尔・莫雷诺
Except for the fact that there's no record
登机入境的记录
of any Rafael Moreno on any inbound flights.
所以他用了假身份证
So he used a fake ID.
所以我让运输安全局去查看
Which is exactly why I've got TSA checking to see
是否有拍到他在机场的快照
if they took any snapshots of him while he was at the airport.
如果我们能确定他乘坐的是哪班飞机
If we can determine what flight he was on,
我们就能知道他用的假名
we can get an alias.
对  在全岛追查他
Right, track him down here on the Island,
看能不能通过他找到巴克福
see if he can lead us to Barkov.
运输安全局来消息了
Hey, this is TSA now.
能抽空和我聊聊吗
you got a second for me?
和你聊一辈子都行
For you I got a whole minute.
谢谢  过来
Thank you. Come here.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
是黛比吗
Deb?
是我
Yeah.
我是凯瑟琳・罗林斯  史蒂夫的朋友
I'm Catherine Rollins; I'm Steve's friend.
只是朋友
Friend?
史蒂夫让我来接你
Steve asked me to, uh, come pick you up
然后送你回他家
and take you back to his place.
他有告诉你别的事情吗
And did he tell you anything else?
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
你有任何需要
If there's anything you need at all,
-尽管开口  好吗  -谢谢
- just please let me know, okay. - Thank you.
我送你回家吧
Let's get you home.
不  我现在  还不想回去
No, I don't... I don't want to go back there just yet.
那你想去哪里
Where would you like to go?
带我去这个岛上最美丽的地方
Take me to the most beautiful spot on the Island.
我刚好知道这个地方
I know just the place.
走吧
Come on.
我需要你的建议
I need some advice.
是关于  我姑妈的
It's, uh, it's about my aunt.
黛比姑妈  她病了
Aunt Deb, she's sick.
病了
She's sick?
你指...
Sick, uh...
她生病了  她得了脑瘤
She's sick; she's got a brain tumor.
我很遗憾  兄弟
I'm sorry, man.
医生怎么说
What, uh, what-what are they gonna do?
这没办法动手术
It's inoperable,
但她拒绝任何其他治疗
but she's refusing any other kind of treatment.
那是她自己的选择吧
I guess that's her choice, right?
是  这是她自己的选择  但问题是
Well, yeah, it's her choice, but here's the thing.
这事不止影响到她自己一个人
I mean, it's not just her who's gonna be affected by this.
玛丽怎么办
I mean, Mary?
失去她  玛丽一定会崩溃的
Mary-Mary's gonna be destroyed if we lose her.
你明白吗
Okay?
先是妈妈展现了拿手好戏  不告而别
First Mom pulls her famous disappearing act again
现在姑妈又病了
and now this?
我该怎么做
What do I do?
我该怎么...怎么才能让她改变主意
How do I... How do I get her to change her mind?
我不这么认为
I don't think, uh,
我觉得你...你不一定要让她改变主意
I don't think you... I don't think you do try to change her mind.
听着  如果这是...
You know, I mean, look, if this...
你们在一起的最后一个感恩节
is your last Thanksgiving together,
难道你想在争吵中度过吗
what, you want to spend it arguing?
当然不想
No.
你想试着留下些回忆
You want to try to make some memories,
一些美好的  永恒的回忆
some good memories, something that's gonna last,
不管接下来发生什么
something that's gonna bring you through
这些回忆能陪伴你走下去
whatever's coming next.
这是我的想法
That's my opinion.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry, man.
运输安全局来消息说
Hey, so TSA came through.
莫雷诺搭乘了昨天的晚间航班
Moreno flew in late last night
用的是迪戈・希尔瓦这个假名
using the name Diego Silva.
同样用这个假名租了辆车
Rented a car using the same alias.
我试着通过定位找到了他
I was able to ping it and get a location.
五零特遣队
Five-O!
Hey, Five-O.
不许动  你敢动试试看
Hey, hey, don't move. Don't you move.
拉斐尔・莫雷诺  你被捕了
Rafael Moreno, you're under arrest.
跪下
Get down on your knees.
把手举到背后  十指交叉
Put your hands behind your head, interlock your fingers.
你认真的吗
Really?
你真觉得你这种蹩脚的小动作会有用吗
You really thought that lame ass move was gonna work?
兄弟  你看起来可比这聪明多了
Brother, you're a lot dumber than you look.
起来
Get up.
史蒂夫  房子其他地方都没人
Steve, the rest of the house is clear.
有些你会感兴趣的东西
There's something you're gonna want to see.
我来看着他  我来看着他
I got him, I got him.
怎么了
What's the matter?
是不是有人击中你了
Somebody shoot you?
看你身上这讨人厌的小伤口
'Cause you got a nasty boo-boo.
看起来巴克福也一直在这里
Looks like Barkov's been staying here as well.
但问题是他现在在哪里
The question is where is he now?
好的
Okay, good.
保持联系
Yeah, keep me posted.
坎贝尔刚和我打完电话
That was Campbell.
特勤处  他们又有麻烦了吗
The Secret Service, did they blink?
空军一号正被转移到科纳
Air Force One is being diverted to Kona,
正如我们所要求的  他们正改变安保细节
and they are pulling the security detail as we speak.
房子那里怎么样了
What about the house?
鉴证科找到巴克福去向的线索了吗
CSU find anything that can tell us where Barkov's headed?
还没有
No, not yet.
他们现在在搜查车库
They're going through the garage right now.
不过他们确实发现了几包碱
They did find a couple bags of lye, though.
他们一定是把鲁索的尸体带到这里来了
This must be where they brought Russo's body.
谢谢  队长
Thanks, Captain.
你要告诉我们巴克福现在在哪里吗
So you gonna tell us where Barkov is?
拉斐尔  我跟你明确一下
Rafael, let me, uh, you know, break it down for you,
因为你看起来很困惑  我帮你整理一下
'cause you seem like you might be confused; I'm here to help you.
你现在是事后从犯  这很糟糕
Uh, you're an accessory after the fact, which is, uh, it's bad.
未参与谋杀  但协助罪犯毁尸灭迹  因此其罪名为事后从犯
有六个国际执法机构想要跟你谈谈
Uh, got about a half dozen international law enforcement agencies
对于那些他们觉得是你干的破事
that want to talk to you, they want to ask you questions
他们有些问题要问你
about some terrible things that they think you've done.
那才刚开始
That's just the beginning.
对啊  更别说
Right, not to mention,
巴克福计划要刺杀总统
Barkov planned to kill the president, too.
我们应该把那个也加进去
We should add that to the list.
什么
What?
我不知道什么总统的事
I don't know nothing about the president.
你当然不知道了
Oh, I'm sure you don't.
你对凯尔・鲁索的事也一无所知吧
Just like you didn't know anything about Kyle Russo, right?
这么说呢  拉斐尔
How about this, Rafael?
你会死在监狱里
You're gonna die in prison.
懂吧
Okay?
但是如果你告诉我们
But if you talk to us,
那么可能  可能我们能帮你
then maybe, maybe we can help you.
我要是告诉你任何关于巴克福的事
I tell you anything about Barkov,
我就会死在他枪口下了
I end up in his crosshairs.
不会  不会  不会
No, no, no.
我们会保护你
We'll protect you.
躲不过他
Not from him.
美极了
It is beautiful.
在海军服役的时候  我到过世界各地
You know, the navy took me all around the world,
但是这里...这里才是家
but this...this is home.
是啊
Yeah.
凯瑟琳
You know, Catherine,
我感觉你会在留在这里的
I got a feeling you're gonna be sticking around for a while.
所以  我能请你帮个忙吗
So, um, can I ask you a favor?
当然可以
Of course.
史蒂夫表面上一副硬汉的形象
You know Steve has that tough guy act down pat.
但其实内心还是
But underneath it all,
那个认为自己失去母亲
he's still that vulnerable little guy
必须快点长大的脆弱的小男孩
who thought he lost his mom and had to grow up too soon.
而玛丽  她是唯一真正了解这一点的人
And Mary, she's the only one who really gets that about him
因为她和他一样
because she lived it, too.
一旦我走了后
Well, once I'm gone,
他们会比以往任何时候都更需要对方
they're gonna need each other more than ever,
即便他们俩都不愿意承认这点
even though they both won't want to admit it.
固执的小孩
Stubborn kids.
所以...
So...
你能照料一下  让他们能走得近点吗
Maybe you could see to it that they stay close?
我会的
I will.
我保证
I promise.
谢谢
Thanks.
史蒂夫  找到一张登机牌
Hey, Steve, found a boarding pass.
是巴克福的化名之一
It's one of Barkov's known aliases.
看看到达时间
Check the arrival time.
巴克福在特勤局开始他们的部署前的
Barkov landed on Oahu 12 hours before the Secret Service
12小时就到瓦胡岛了
even started their canvass.
所以要么这家伙会通灵...
So either this guy is psychic...
要么他的目标不是总统
Or the president is not the target.
他是冲其他人来的
He's after somebody else.
谁是目标
Who's the target, huh?
谁是真正的目标
Who's the real target?
怎么了  巴克福来这不是为了总统
Hey, what's going on? Barkov's not here
他来是有别的活
for the president-- he's on a job.
对啊  鉴于巴克福有需要时
That's right. And since Barkov called Moreno here
就把莫雷诺叫来了
when he needed help,
我在想那工作可能是为
I'm thinking that job was for
他阿尔巴尼亚的老朋友做的
his old friends back in Albania.
你会告诉我他真正的目标是谁吧
You gonna tell me who the real target is?
弟兄们  清场
Huh? Guys, clear out.
鉴证科  快点  给他清场
CSU, come on. Let's clear out.
高品质碱
得了  干嘛  你准备现在用水刑吗
Come on, what, are you gonna waterboard me now?
我可不这么认为
I don't think so.
怎么回事  不  不...
What's going on? No, no...
怎么回事  你告诉我们或者你被烧
What's going on: you're gonna talk or you're gonna burn.
懂了吗
You understand?
等等  等等  你不能这么做
Wait, wait. You can't do this! Hey!
谁是目标  谁才是目标
Who's the target? Who's the target?!
谁是目标
Who's the target?! Huh?!
好了  好了  好了
Okay, okay, okay!
行了  巴克福的目标是
Okay. Barkov's target is
-一个在凯卢阿的女人  -还不够
- a woman in Kailua. - Not enough!
安德莉娅・希克斯  安德莉娅・希克斯
Andrea Hicks! Andrea Hicks!
我只知道这么多
That's all I know!
等一下  等一下
Hold on, hold on. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
那个多事的邻居
Hey. The nosy neighbor.
给我们描述巴克福的人
The one who gave us Barkov's description.
她的女儿叫安德莉娅
Her daughter's name was Andrea.
她做了什么会遭到袭击
What did she do to warrant a hit?
我不知道  我没问
I don't know and I didn't ask.
但在完成任务前  巴克福是不会离开的
But Barkov won't leave the Island till the job is done.
希拉・希克斯家没人接电话
No answer at Sheila Hicks'.
凯瑟琳  你找到什么了
Catherine, what do you got?
我一直在调查安德莉娅・希克斯
Okay, so I've been looking into Andrea Hicks.
直到两个月以前  她一直住在达拉斯
Up until two months ago, she was living in Dallas,
她是个牙医  然后...
working as a dental hygienist. Then...
就没有她的消息了
she just dropped off the grid.
知道为什么吗
Do we know why?
根据联调局的信息
Well, according to the FBI,
她目睹了一个俄罗斯犯罪集团的
she witnessed the murder of a high-ranking member
高级成员被杀
of a Russian crime family.
联调局的人想跟她谈谈
The Feds wanted to talk to her--
她却选择躲起来
she went into hiding instead.
好吧  然后同时这个犯罪集团
Okay, and meanwhile the family,
雇佣了巴克福去找到她
they hire Barkov to track her down
让她永远开不了口
and shut her up,permanently.
好  凯瑟琳  听我说
All right, Catherine, listen to me.
你继续找安德莉娅
You keep trying to find Andrea, okay?
我们快到凯卢阿了
We're almost in Kailua.
好  马上去办
Yeah, you got it.
我们必须赶快离开这
We need to get out of here.
什么
What?
妈妈  快点...
Mom, come on...
树林里传来的
Came from the woods.
在周围拉好警戒
Secure the perimeter.
我们要把这封锁起来  让你的人就位
We need to lock it down. Get your men in position.
听到他说的了吧  赶快行动
All right, you heard the man. Let's move out.
那里  那里  那里
There, there, there.
天呐
Oh, my God!
丹尼
Danny!
好了  好了
Okay, okay.
她会没事的
She's gonna be okay.
她没事的  没事的
She's gonna be okay, all right.
她被打中了一边肩膀  没事的
One of the shoulders. She'll be all right.
珍珠港-希卡姆联合基地
怎么回事
What's the matter?
你还好吗
You all right?
我怎么会不好呢
Why wouldn't I be all right?
你看上去有点紧张
Well, you do seem a little nervous.
紧张吗
Nervous?
没有啦  我们马上就要见到总统了
Oh, no, no. We're about to meet the President.
你们怎么能这么镇定  这才是该问的问题
Why are you so zen? That's a better question.
问你们呢
All of you.
我一向这么酷
I'm just cool like that.
要知道  总统是本地人
You know, the President's a local boy.
我们就像他的禁卫军
That makes us practically Hoapili.
搞不懂你在说什么
I don't know what that means.
我也很紧张  在第一次见他的时候
I was nervous, too, the first time.
"第一次见他的时候"
"The first time"?
你什么时候见过总统
When'd you meet the President?
无可奉告
I can't tell you that.
那是机密
It's classified.
机密  是吗
Oh, it's classified, huh? Oh.
是在草莓地行动的时候吗
Was it during, uh, Operation Strawberry Fields?
我已经说太多了
I've already said too much.
我看起来怎么样  正式吗
How do I look? I look all right?
帅呆了
Yeah, you look very handsome.
谢谢
Thank you.
你也很帅
You do, too.
谢谢
Thank you.
终于来了  美国的英雄们  看看你们
Here they are, America's heroes. Look at you.
不用谢我们
No thanks necessary.
都是分内的事
All in a day's work.
不过那些长板我要一个  谢谢
I will take one of those longboards though. Thank you.
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
谢了  老兄
Thank you, brother.
让我们举杯
All right, I want to make a toast.
为我们能够让世人安心地
Uh, making the world safer for
吃上火鸡和苹果派干杯
turkey and apple pie, that's us.
说到火鸡和苹果派  晚餐在哪儿
Speaking of turkey and apple pie, where's dinner?
那个  我和玛丽
Well, I'm afraid, uh, Mary and I struck out,
出去买火鸡的时候
uh, when it came to finding a turkey
没找到够我们大家吃的大火鸡
big enough to feed everybody here.
但善良的卡玛科纳为了弥补这个缺失
But Kamekona here has graciously offered
为我们拿来了  一锅虾煲
to fix... A shrimp casserole.
你们拯救世界
Hey, you guys save the world,
而我拯救了晚餐
I'll save supper.
不行  绝对不行
No, absolutely not.
感恩节怎么能吃虾
We're not eating shrimp for Thanksgiving.
乞丐可没有选择权
Beggars can't be choosers, brah.
不  他们有得选
Actually, they can.
我有对策
Uh, I have a contingency plan.
是吗  什么对策
Really? What kind of plan?
无可奉告  那是机密
I can't tell you, it's classified.
机密还真不少
Again with the classified, huh?
我告诉玛丽了
I had the talk with Mary.
她反应如何
How'd she take it?
她是个坚强的女孩
She's a strong girl,
但我觉得  现在她需要哥哥的安慰
but I think right now, she needs her brother.
我们会度过这道坎的
We're gonna get through this.
对吗
Yeah?
我只是为琼感到难过
I just feel so bad for Joan.
她还那么小  她都不会记得她的姑婆
She's so young, and she's not gonna remember her nanny.
我了解  但没事的
I know. It's okay though.
我们可以给她讲黛比姑婆的事
We're gonna tell her all about Aunt Deb.
我们会告诉她  她的姑婆有多爱我们
We're gonna tell her all about how much she loved us.
好吗
All right?
火鸡的事情  对不起
I'm really sorry about the turkey.
没事
Come on.
今晚这已经是最好的结局了
That's the best thing that could've happened.
火奴鲁鲁  拉玛丽安娜夏威夷风情酒吧
伙计们  你们真是好观众
Boy, you're a great audience.
既然你们如此出色
And because you're a great audience,
我要给你们一个特别的惊喜
I got a special surprise for you.
他不会又要讲辛纳屈的故事吧
Is he gonna tell that Sinatra story again?
著名美国歌手  歌坛元老级人物
看样子不是
No, I don't think so.
很久  很久以前
Many, many years ago,
我的好兄弟约翰・麦格瑞特总是向我吹嘘
my good friend John McGarrett used to brag about
他的妹妹在洛杉矶那些传奇俱乐部里献唱
his sister singing in these legendary nightclubs
比如卡德罗俱乐部
in Los Angeles, like the Trocadero,
仙乐斯和椰林酒吧
Ciro's and the Cocoanut Grove.
那些音韵绕梁三日不止
And the beat goes on and on.
但我从没听过她的歌声
Well, I never got to hear her.
但命运使然
But as fate has it,
今晚  在这里
right here tonight in this club,
黛比・麦格瑞特大驾光临
we have... Deb McGarrett.
黛比  能请你为台下的观众们
Deb, would you please come up and sing a song
献上一曲吗
for this marvelous audience?
这是你计划的
You plan this?
只是想制造些回忆
Just making some memories, right?
我真没想到会让我上台
Well, I certainly didn't expect this.
我已经很久没唱过歌了
I mean, I haven't sung in, well...
上次唱歌就像在一百年前...
about a hundred years, and, uh...
嗓子也不如当年
Well, these old pipes are pretty rusty.
但既然这是个特别的场合
But, uh, since it's a special occasion,
罢了罢了
oh, what the hell.
我想将这首歌献给我的家人
I'd like to dedicate this song to my family,
我的亲人们  史蒂夫  玛丽和小琼宝贝
my little ohana, Steve, Mary and baby Joanie.
我爱你们  非常爱
I love you all so very much.
开始吧  献丑了
Here goes. Bear with me.
乐队
Maestro.
清点我的所有*
*Taking stock of what I have and what I haven't
我发现*
*What do I find
我所拥有的会让我幸福*
*The things I've got will keep me satisfied
仔细检查我的所有*
*Checking up on what I have and what I haven't
我发现*
*What do I find
我不曾欠人钱物*
*A healthy balance on the credit side
既无钻石  也无珍珠*
*Got no diamond, got no pearl
但我仍是幸运的姑娘*
*Still I think I'm a lucky girl
晨光照耀*
*I've got the sun in the morning
月光陪伴*
*And the moon at night
既无金  也无银*
*Got no silver, got no gold
我的东西都是无价之宝*
*What I've got can't be bought or sold
晨光照耀*
*I've got the sun in the morning
月光陪伴*
*And the moon at night
阳光赐我美好一天*
*Sunshine gives me a lovely day
月光赐我闪亮银河*
*Moonlight gives me the Milky Way
既无钻石  也无珍珠*
*Got no diamond, got no pearl
我仍是个幸运的姑娘*
*Still I think I'm a lucky girl
晨光照耀*
*And with the sun in the morning
月光陪伴*
*And the moon in the evening
让我事事顺心*
*I'm all right.